Hello Namaskar friends, a very hearty
welcome to our YouTube
channel, friends, today's video is going to be very
special for you, so in today's
video I am going to talk to you about how you will be able to pay the
live insurance of ICC potential
online,
friends, how will you be able to deposit it, so
in this video I am going to tell you that you people
can pay the live insurance of ICIC potential online yourself, friends,
and here you will also be able to check how much
money you have received and how you have to deposit it.
In this video I am going to
guide you step by step.
Friends, I will
tell you exactly how the IC
potential, which is live insurance, is deposited.  Sometimes you
people face a lot of problems here as to
how you should
not face any problem while filling life insurance, that is why I am making a video for you
friends.  So do
n't skip the video at all.  Friends,
you must watch the video from beginning to end.
So friends, let's start today's video.
So let's start
friends, before starting the video, if you are
new to the channel then do subscribe to the channel for such new updates
and after subscribing also press the bell icon
so that all my notifications can
reach you, I keep bringing such new updates to you
daily, so
friends, after subscribing to the channel, if you liked the video then please
like the video, friends, so
let's start today's video, so
friends, you will have to go to the home screen on your phone
and first of all
you need an app whose
name is Google Pay and it is
currently available in everyone's phone,
Google Pay, so friends, you just have to open Google Pay
and through that your
life insurance, your SSC
potential, is going to be paid from here.
Ok?  Now I will go there and
tell you how to fill it.
You will be
able to fill it easily from there in just one click.  Ok?  So
friends, I want to see Google Pay here,
you will have to go to your phone.  Those who do
not have Google Pay in their phones, please
download it and after downloading it,
I will simply open it.
So friends, as I opened it,
after opening it, see, everything is
logged in etc. here.  Ok?  So friends, after logging in,
scroll down a bit here and here you will
see the option of Bill and Bill and Recharge.
Ok?
So the option of bill and recharge will be
visible here.  So here you will
see the option of LIC Life Insurance also.  So
you just have to click on LIC Life Insurance and enter it.
So see, as I enter,
after entering, friends, all the
LSC running in India,
okay, you get
to see all of them available here, so see
friends, here the LSC which we have to fill is of
SSC Potential Life Insurance,
so see here you can see it on the third number itself, so
see friends, to
fill SSC Potential Life Insurance,
you just have to click here, okay, so friends, as
soon as you click here,
see, I also filled the life
insurance of SSC Pad, I was facing
some problems in it, so that is why
I have brought its session, friends,
how you have to fill it correctly, so see,
I am going to tell you now, so do
not skip the video at all,
friends, do watch the video completely, so
see friends, what you have to do,
after this, here it is asking you for the policy number,
date of birth and nickname here,
okay, so first we will enter the policy number,
if you do not know the policy number, then
whatever you might have got filled from the agent or
you can go anywhere and directly get it.  If you have
submitted it then you should already know the policy number there
because without the policy number you will
not be able to fill it here.  Ok?  So policy number one, whatever you get
filled by the agent etc.,
they themselves give it to you.  There they
give a slip with LIC number in
it in which everything like date of birth, name etc. is
written.  Ok?  And if you have
already filled it online and you get a message
on your phone, you will be able to see the policy number
on your phone itself.  So
you will have to enter that policy number here.
Ok?  After that friends, you have to
enter the date of birth here.  The main thing is to
enter the date of birth here.
I will tell you in which format you have to enter it.  So
friends, you have to
enter the format like this.  Like it is written here in
D D M O N Y YY
format.  Ok?  You have to enter it in this format.
As you can see, it is
written here Enter.  Look here, the
date 31st is entered here.  Then
January is mentioned here.  Then 1990 is inserted.
Ok?  So see, you have to put it like this.
Like 31, you entered
any date randomly.  After that you have to put a dash here.
Then January has to be entered.  Then you have to
put a dash.  Then you can enter whatever you want here, 19990 91 92.
Ok?  So you have to
enter it in this format.  Only then
your date of birth will be
selected here.  Ok?  Because I was
also filling it here, I had also
filled it here, I had tried to fill life insurance on SSC potential but it was
not
taking it.  Did it once or twice, didn't I take it?
After that I saw the format here.  Here
you have to enter the format in this way.
So after this I put it in this format and it became
mine.  Ok?
After that friends, you will enter the date of birth and
policy number here.  After that,
whatever will be your nickname of ICC Potential
in life insurance, you will have to
enter that name here.
Friends, after entering the name, if you click on the option of continue here, then the
amount of money pending in your SSC portage will be
written there and till what
date your expiry will be, it will also be
written in all your details here
and as it remains pending there, then the
option of pay now also comes there.
You can deposit it directly from wherever you are.
Ok?  By doing K Pay Now, you
can directly get the money deducted from there and deposit it in your bank.  Ok?  So
friends, if your payment is pending there and it gets done then it will be
written as successful there.  After that the option of No Dues will
appear there.  Meaning that there
is no payment left.  This is how I will write for you,
friends.  So friends, in this way, I have told you to fill the ICC
Potential Life Insurance
yourself online.
Friends, if you
still have any query then please
comment in the comment box.  I will
definitely try to give you a session, friends.
So see you in the next video.  Friends,
if you liked the video then
please like the video and subscribe to the channel.
See you in the next video
friends.